author:	Inrixia
association:	owner
edited:	false
status:	none
--
Looks good. Happy to merge but please bump minor version.

Also there is a observer helper in the Luna lib which if you can switch to it would be preferable. But no worries if it's not applicable.

Thanks ?뮏

Once the version is bumped I'll merge. 
--
author:	Inrixia
association:	owner
edited:	false
status:	changes requested
--
Bump minor version
--
